<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Android Tips on Matiuswedos</title>
    <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/android-tips/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Android Tips on Matiuswedos</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/android-tips/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Instantly Turn Off Magnifier On Your Android Phone!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-instantly-turn-off-magnifier-on-your-android-phone-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-instantly-turn-off-magnifier-on-your-android-phone-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you tired of the magnifier on your Android phone always turning on when you least expect it? It can be a real hassle, especially if you don&amp;rsquo;t need it or don&amp;rsquo;t know how to turn it off. Fortunately, there is a simple trick that will instantly turn off the magnifier on your Android phone.
Steps to Turn Off Magnifier on Android Phone The first step is to open the Settings app on your Android phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlock the Secret to Taking Epic Long Screenshots on Android 12!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secret-to-taking-epic-long-screenshots-on-android-12-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secret-to-taking-epic-long-screenshots-on-android-12-/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the Secret to Taking Epic Long Screenshots on Android 12! We all know how useful screenshots can be when it comes to quickly capturing important information, conversations, and more. But what if you need to capture something that’s longer than a single page? That’s where long screenshots come in!
Long screenshots, also known as scrolling screenshots, are a great way to capture long conversations, webpages, articles, and other long pieces of information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This 1 Simple Trick Will Make Sure You Never Accidentally Rotate Your Android Screen Again!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/this-1-simple-trick-will-make-sure-you-never-accidentally-rotate-your-android-screen-again-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/this-1-simple-trick-will-make-sure-you-never-accidentally-rotate-your-android-screen-again-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction If you&amp;rsquo;re like most Android users, you&amp;rsquo;ve probably had the experience of accidentally rotating your screen when you didn&amp;rsquo;t want to. This can be a real pain, especially if you&amp;rsquo;re in the middle of something important. Fortunately, there&amp;rsquo;s a simple trick that you can use to make sure this never happens again.
Overview of the Problem When you rotate your Android device, the screen automatically rotates to match the orientation of the device.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
