<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Contests on Matiuswedos</title>
    <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/contests/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Contests on Matiuswedos</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/contests/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When You Play Tim Hortons Roll Up the Rim to Win!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-play-tim-hortons-roll-up-the-rim-to-win-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-play-tim-hortons-roll-up-the-rim-to-win-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for an exciting way to win fantastic prizes? Then you should definitely check out Tim Hortons Roll Up the Rim to Win! This popular promotion has been around for years and is a great way to get your hands on some awesome prizes.
Overview of Tim Hortons Roll Up the Rim to Win Tim Hortons Roll Up the Rim to Win is an annual promotion that takes place at participating Tim Hortons locations in Canada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What You Could Win on Roll Up the Rim - Find Out Now!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-you-could-win-on-roll-up-the-rim-find-out-now-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-you-could-win-on-roll-up-the-rim-find-out-now-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Roll Up the Rim is an annual promotion by Tim Hortons that has been running for over 30 years. It&amp;rsquo;s a great way to get excited about coffee, and you could even win some amazing prizes!
Overview of Roll Up the Rim Roll Up the Rim is a promotion that runs from February to April each year. Customers purchase specially marked coffee cups from participating Tim Hortons locations, and have the chance to win prizes when they roll up the rim of the cup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy It Is To Check If You&#39;ve Won Roll Up The Rim To Win!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-check-if-you-ve-won-roll-up-the-rim-to-win-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-check-if-you-ve-won-roll-up-the-rim-to-win-/</guid>
      <description>You Won&amp;rsquo;t Believe How Easy It Is To Check If You&amp;rsquo;ve Won Roll Up The Rim To Win! Roll Up The Rim To Win is a fun and exciting way to win amazing prizes from your favorite coffee shop, Tim Hortons. Every year, millions of Canadians take part in this contest and try their luck at winning one of the many prizes offered. But how do you know if you&amp;rsquo;ve won?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlock the Secrets of Scanning Roll Up the Rim to Win - Learn How Now!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secrets-of-scanning-roll-up-the-rim-to-win-learn-how-now-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secrets-of-scanning-roll-up-the-rim-to-win-learn-how-now-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Do you want to unlock the secrets of scanning Roll Up the Rim to Win? Have you heard of the popular Canadian game that allows you to win great prizes just by scanning your eligible products? Read on to learn more about how you can participate in this fun game and the benefits of scanning Roll Up the Rim to Win!
Overview of Scanning Roll Up the Rim to Win Scanning Roll Up the Rim to Win is a popular Canadian game that allows you to win great prizes just by scanning your eligible products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When You Play Roll Up the Rim to Win!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-play-roll-up-the-rim-to-win-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-play-roll-up-the-rim-to-win-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Roll Up the Rim to Win is a popular game in Canada that has been around since 1986. It&amp;rsquo;s a fun and exciting way to win prizes while enjoying a delicious cup of coffee. This blog post will explain what Roll Up the Rim to Win is, the benefits of playing, and the excitement of participating.
Overview of Roll Up the Rim to Win Roll Up the Rim to Win is a promotion run by Tim Hortons every year from March to April.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
