<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Humor on Matiuswedos</title>
    <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/humor/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Humor on Matiuswedos</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/humor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When You Try Eating Spaghetti With Chopsticks!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-try-eating-spaghetti-with-chopsticks-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-try-eating-spaghetti-with-chopsticks-/</guid>
      <description>You Won&amp;rsquo;t Believe What Happens When You Try Eating Spaghetti With Chopsticks! Have you ever wondered what would happen if you tried to eat spaghetti with chopsticks? We decided to find out! In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explain the process of our experiment, the results, and our final conclusions.
I. Introduction A. Definition of Spaghetti: Spaghetti is a type of pasta that is usually made from durum wheat and water. It is usually cooked by boiling and is usually served with a sauce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happened When This Person Lost Their Samsung S21!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-this-person-lost-their-samsung-s21-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-this-person-lost-their-samsung-s21-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction We all know how frustrating it can be to lose something important, like a phone. That’s why it’s always important to make sure you keep your devices safe and secure. But what happens when you can’t find your phone? That’s exactly what happened to one person who recently lost their Samsung S21.
The Search for the Lost Phone The person in question had been searching for their lost phone for days without any luck.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Reddit User Found a Clever Way to Fake Their iPhone Location - You Won&#39;t Believe What Happened Next!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/this-reddit-user-found-a-clever-way-to-fake-their-iphone-location-you-won-t-believe-what-happened-next-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/this-reddit-user-found-a-clever-way-to-fake-their-iphone-location-you-won-t-believe-what-happened-next-/</guid>
      <description>This Reddit User Found a Clever Way to Fake Their iPhone Location - You Won&amp;rsquo;t Believe What Happened Next! I. Introduction A Reddit user recently found a clever way to fake their iPhone location, and the outcome of their actions left many users stunned. In this blog post, we’ll take a look at the details of the Reddit user’s scheme, the consequences of their actions, and the reaction of others to their actions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
