<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Mobile Photography on Matiuswedos</title>
    <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/mobile-photography/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mobile Photography on Matiuswedos</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/mobile-photography/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Let You Blur Backgrounds on Your iPhone Without Portrait Mode!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-let-you-blur-backgrounds-on-your-iphone-without-portrait-mode-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-let-you-blur-backgrounds-on-your-iphone-without-portrait-mode-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction We all love to take pictures with our iPhones, but sometimes we want more than just a basic photo. Blurring the background is a popular way to make your photos look more professional and artistic. Unfortunately, this usually requires a phone with a portrait mode, which can be expensive. Fortunately, there is a simple trick that you can use to blur backgrounds on your iPhone without needing portrait mode!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlock the Secret to Capturing Every Moment on Your iPhone 7 Plus - Learn How to Set Screen Record Now!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secret-to-capturing-every-moment-on-your-iphone-7-plus-learn-how-to-set-screen-record-now-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secret-to-capturing-every-moment-on-your-iphone-7-plus-learn-how-to-set-screen-record-now-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for a way to capture every moment of your life on your iPhone 7 Plus? If so, you’re in luck! With the introduction of the new iOS 11, Apple has added a feature called Screen Record, which allows you to record your screen and capture any moment with ease. In this blog post, we’ll explore the benefits of using the iPhone 7 Plus for capturing moments and provide a step-by-step guide for setting up Screen Record.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
