<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Notification Settings on Matiuswedos</title>
    <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/notification-settings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Notification Settings on Matiuswedos</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/notification-settings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy It Is To Unsilence Notifications On Your iPhone For Just One Person!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-unsilence-notifications-on-your-iphone-for-just-one-person-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-unsilence-notifications-on-your-iphone-for-just-one-person-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever wanted to unsilence notifications on your iPhone for just one person? It can be really annoying when you have a bunch of notifications coming in from people you don’t really care about, but you don’t want to miss out on important messages from the people you do care about. Luckily, you can now unsilence notifications on your iPhone for just one person so you can stay up to date with the people you care about without being bombarded with notifications from people you don’t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy It Is To Turn Off Silent Mode Notifications On Your iPhone!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-turn-off-silent-mode-notifications-on-your-iphone-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-turn-off-silent-mode-notifications-on-your-iphone-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you tired of being bombarded with notifications on your iPhone, even when you&amp;rsquo;re in silent mode? We have good news for you - turning off silent mode notifications is easier than you think! In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through how to turn off silent mode notifications on your iPhone and explain the benefits of doing so.
Overview of Silent Mode Notifications Silent mode notifications are notifications that appear on your iPhone even when you have your phone set to silent mode.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
