<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>iPhone 12 on Matiuswedos</title>
    <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/iphone-12/</link>
    <description>Recent content in iPhone 12 on Matiuswedos</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/iphone-12/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy it is to Turn Off Your iPhone 12 Flashlight for Messages!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-turn-off-your-iphone-12-flashlight-for-messages-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-turn-off-your-iphone-12-flashlight-for-messages-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Do you have an iPhone 12 and want to turn off the flashlight for messages? If so, you are in luck! Turning off the flashlight for messages on your iPhone 12 is surprisingly easy and can be done in just a few steps. In this blog post, we will discuss what the flashlight for messages is, the benefits of turning it off, and the steps to turn it off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy It Is to Take Off SOS on iPhone 12!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-take-off-sos-on-iphone-12-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-take-off-sos-on-iphone-12-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you a proud owner of the new iPhone 12? If so, you may have noticed the SOS feature that is enabled by default. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explain what SOS is and why you should turn it off, as well as provide step-by-step instructions on how to do so.
Definition of SOS SOS (or &amp;ldquo;Safety of Life at Sea&amp;rdquo;) is a feature that was designed to help people who are in distress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy it is to Fix SOS Only on iPhone 12!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-fix-sos-only-on-iphone-12-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-fix-sos-only-on-iphone-12-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction If you&amp;rsquo;re an iPhone 12 user, you may have seen the SOS Only message appear on your device. This message can be confusing and can be difficult to fix. Fortunately, it&amp;rsquo;s actually quite easy to fix the SOS Only message on your iPhone 12. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explain what the SOS Only message is, the benefits of fixing it, and the steps you need to take to fix it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unglaubliche Methode: So kannst du dein iPhone 12 ohne Display ausschalten!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unglaubliche-methode-so-kannst-du-dein-iphone-12-ohne-display-ausschalten-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unglaubliche-methode-so-kannst-du-dein-iphone-12-ohne-display-ausschalten-/</guid>
      <description>Unglaubliche Methode: So kannst du dein iPhone 12 ohne Display ausschalten! Einleitung Es ist eine bekannte Tatsache, dass iPhones sehr kostspielig sind. Daher möchten die meisten Menschen sicherstellen, dass sie ihr Gerät so lange wie möglich benutzen können. Ein Problem, das viele iPhone-Nutzer haben, ist, dass das Display ihres iPhones ausgefallen ist. Dieses Problem ist besonders bei iPhone 12-Benutzern verbreitet. Da das Display des iPhones 12 nicht mehr funktioniert, können sie es nicht mehr ausschalten.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
