<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Computer Hardware on Matiuswedos</title>
    <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/computer-hardware/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Computer Hardware on Matiuswedos</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/computer-hardware/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy It Is to Take a Screenshot on Your Windows 7 Toshiba Laptop!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-take-a-screenshot-on-your-windows-7-toshiba-laptop-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-take-a-screenshot-on-your-windows-7-toshiba-laptop-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Do you have a Toshiba laptop with Windows 7? Have you ever wanted to take a screenshot of something you see on your laptop screen? If so, you’re in luck! Taking a screenshot on your Toshiba laptop with Windows 7 is surprisingly easy. Read on to learn how.
What is a Screenshot? A screenshot is an image of what is currently displayed on your laptop screen. It can be used to capture something you want to save or share with someone else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy It Is to Take Screenshots on a Lenovo Laptop with Windows 11!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-take-screenshots-on-a-lenovo-laptop-with-windows-11-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-take-screenshots-on-a-lenovo-laptop-with-windows-11-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Taking screenshots on a laptop can be a great way to capture a moment or document something important. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re troubleshooting a technical issue or just want to show off something cool, screenshots are a great way to share information with others. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss how to take screenshots on a Lenovo laptop with Windows 11.
Definition of Screenshots A screenshot is a digital image of what is currently displayed on a computer monitor, television, or other visual output device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revolutionize Your Setup: Use an Android Tablet as a Monitor on Linux via USB!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/revolutionize-your-setup-use-an-android-tablet-as-a-monitor-on-linux-via-usb-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/revolutionize-your-setup-use-an-android-tablet-as-a-monitor-on-linux-via-usb-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for a way to revolutionize your Linux setup? If so, then you should consider using an Android tablet as a monitor on Linux via USB! In this blog post, we will discuss the definition of an Android tablet, the benefits of using one as a monitor on Linux, and an overview of what is needed to set it up. We will also go over the steps required to set up the Android tablet, including connecting the tablet to the computer, installing necessary software, and configuring the system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy it is to Take a Screenshot on a Lenovo ThinkPad Laptop with Windows 7!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-take-a-screenshot-on-a-lenovo-thinkpad-laptop-with-windows-7-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-take-a-screenshot-on-a-lenovo-thinkpad-laptop-with-windows-7-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you a Lenovo ThinkPad laptop user with Windows 7? Have you ever wanted to take a screenshot of something you see on your computer? If so, you’ll be glad to know that taking a screenshot on a Lenovo ThinkPad laptop with Windows 7 is easy! In this blog post, we’ll explain what a screenshot is, the benefits of taking a screenshot, and the steps to take a screenshot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlock the Secret: Discover How to Easily Print Screen on Your Toshiba Laptop Running Windows 7!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secret-discover-how-to-easily-print-screen-on-your-toshiba-laptop-running-windows-7-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secret-discover-how-to-easily-print-screen-on-your-toshiba-laptop-running-windows-7-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Printing a screenshot of your Toshiba laptop running Windows 7 is an easy task that can save a lot of time when you need to share or keep a record of something on your computer. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll explain the definition of print screen, the benefits of knowing how to print screen, and the steps to print screen on a Toshiba laptop running Windows 7.
Definition of Print Screen Print screen is the process of capturing an image of what is currently displayed on your computer screen.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
