<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Software Troubleshooting on Matiuswedos</title>
    <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/software-troubleshooting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Software Troubleshooting on Matiuswedos</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/software-troubleshooting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Unbelievable Trick: How to Enable USB Debugging on Android Device with Broken Screen!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unbelievable-trick-how-to-enable-usb-debugging-on-android-device-with-broken-screen-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unbelievable-trick-how-to-enable-usb-debugging-on-android-device-with-broken-screen-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever encountered a situation where you need to enable USB debugging on an Android device with a broken screen? This can be a real headache as you cannot access the device&amp;rsquo;s settings to enable USB debugging. Fortunately, there is a trick that can help you out. In this blog post, we will discuss how to enable USB debugging on Android devices with broken screens.
Definition of USB Debugging USB debugging is a feature that is used to allow communication between an Android device and a computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tired of Split Screen? Here&#39;s the Easy Way to Turn it Off on Your Android Phone!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/tired-of-split-screen-here-s-the-easy-way-to-turn-it-off-on-your-android-phone-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/tired-of-split-screen-here-s-the-easy-way-to-turn-it-off-on-your-android-phone-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Turning Off Split Screen on Android Split screen is a feature on Android phones that allows you to view two apps at the same time. While this can be a helpful feature for multitasking, it can also be annoying if you don&amp;rsquo;t want to use it. Fortunately, turning off split screen on your Android phone is easy!
Benefits of Turning Off Split Screen Turning off split screen can help you save battery life, as it will reduce the amount of processing power your phone needs to run two apps at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlock the Secrets of Screenshots on Your Lenovo Laptop with Windows 11!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secrets-of-screenshots-on-your-lenovo-laptop-with-windows-11-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secrets-of-screenshots-on-your-lenovo-laptop-with-windows-11-/</guid>
      <description>IV. Conclusion
Introduction to Screenshots on Windows 11 If you’re a Lenovo laptop user running Windows 11, you may not be aware of the powerful screenshot tools at your disposal. Taking and editing screenshots can be a great way to capture and share important information quickly and easily. In this blog post, we’ll explore the basics of taking and editing screenshots on Windows 11 and provide tips on how to share them with others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Surprise! Here&#39;s the Secret to Easily Turning Off Safe Mode on Your Android Box</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/surprise-here-s-the-secret-to-easily-turning-off-safe-mode-on-your-android-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/surprise-here-s-the-secret-to-easily-turning-off-safe-mode-on-your-android-box/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever found your Android box stuck in Safe Mode? It can be a frustrating experience, but don&amp;rsquo;t worry! We&amp;rsquo;ve got the secret to quickly and easily turning off Safe Mode on your Android box.
What is Safe Mode? Safe Mode is a special mode that can be enabled on your Android box to help troubleshoot and diagnose issues. When in Safe Mode, only the essential apps and services are allowed to run, and no third-party apps can be installed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy It Is to Take Off SOS on iPhone 12!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-take-off-sos-on-iphone-12-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-take-off-sos-on-iphone-12-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you a proud owner of the new iPhone 12? If so, you may have noticed the SOS feature that is enabled by default. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explain what SOS is and why you should turn it off, as well as provide step-by-step instructions on how to do so.
Definition of SOS SOS (or &amp;ldquo;Safety of Life at Sea&amp;rdquo;) is a feature that was designed to help people who are in distress.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
