<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Photography on Matiuswedos</title>
    <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/photography/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Photography on Matiuswedos</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/photography/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Unlock the Hidden Power of Your Android Camera: Discover How to Enable QR Code Scanning!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unlock-the-hidden-power-of-your-android-camera-discover-how-to-enable-qr-code-scanning-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unlock-the-hidden-power-of-your-android-camera-discover-how-to-enable-qr-code-scanning-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for a way to quickly and easily access important information on your Android device? Look no further than the power of QR codes! QR codes are a type of barcode that can be scanned by your device’s camera to quickly and easily access information. In this blog post, we’ll explain what QR codes are, the benefits of using them, how to set up QR code scanning on your Android device, and some tips for using QR code scanning on your Android device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Make Your iPhone 13 Pro Max Photos Pop - Learn How to Blur the Background Instantly!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-make-your-iphone-13-pro-max-photos-pop-learn-how-to-blur-the-background-instantly-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-make-your-iphone-13-pro-max-photos-pop-learn-how-to-blur-the-background-instantly-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for a way to make your iPhone 13 Pro Max photos look more professional? We&amp;rsquo;ve got a great trick for you! Blurring the background of your photos is an easy way to instantly make your photos look more polished and professional. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explain what blurring the background is and how to do it on the iPhone 13 Pro Max.
Benefits of Blurring the Background Blurring the background of your photos can have a huge impact on the overall look and feel of the photo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Make Your iPhone Videos Look Professional - Create Blur Background Videos Instantly!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-make-your-iphone-videos-look-professional-create-blur-background-videos-instantly-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-make-your-iphone-videos-look-professional-create-blur-background-videos-instantly-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for an easy way to make your iPhone videos look more professional? Then you’re in luck! This simple trick will help you create blur background videos instantly.
Overview of the Trick This trick involves using the Portrait Mode setting on your iPhone to create blur background videos. It’s a quick and easy way to make your videos look more professional without having to invest in expensive equipment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy It Is To Blur Backgrounds On iPhone 14!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-blur-backgrounds-on-iphone-14-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-blur-backgrounds-on-iphone-14-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for an easy way to blur the background of your photos on your iPhone 14? If so, you&amp;rsquo;re in luck! In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll show you how to blur backgrounds on your iPhone 14 in just a few easy steps.
What is Blurring Backgrounds? Blurring backgrounds is a photography technique that involves softening the background of a photo to draw attention to the subject. This is done by using a shallow depth of field, which is when the camera focuses on a single object while blurring out the background.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe the Results of This Camera Comparison Between the iPhone 14 Plus and iPhone 13 Pro Max!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-the-results-of-this-camera-comparison-between-the-iphone-14-plus-and-iphone-13-pro-max-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-the-results-of-this-camera-comparison-between-the-iphone-14-plus-and-iphone-13-pro-max-/</guid>
      <description>You Won&amp;rsquo;t Believe the Results of This Camera Comparison Between the iPhone 14 Plus and iPhone 13 Pro Max! As Apple continues to make strides in smartphone camera technology, it can be difficult to keep up with the latest advancements. To help you make an informed decision when comparing the iPhone 14 Plus and iPhone 13 Pro Max, we’ve put together a comprehensive camera comparison.
Introduction A. Overview of the comparison between iPhone 14 Plus and iPhone 13 Pro Max</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy It Is to Blur Your Background on the iPhone 14!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-blur-your-background-on-the-iphone-14-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-blur-your-background-on-the-iphone-14-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The new iPhone 14 is here, and it&amp;rsquo;s packed with amazing features. One of the most exciting features of the iPhone 14 is the ability to blur your background in photos. Blurring your background can give your photos a professional look, and it&amp;rsquo;s surprisingly easy to do with the iPhone 14. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the benefits of blurring your background on the iPhone 14 and provide a step-by-step tutorial on how to do it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlock the Secret: Discover How to Blur Backgrounds on Your iPhone 14 Pro Max!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secret-discover-how-to-blur-backgrounds-on-your-iphone-14-pro-max-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secret-discover-how-to-blur-backgrounds-on-your-iphone-14-pro-max-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Do you want to take your iPhone photography to the next level? If so, you’ve come to the right place! Blurring backgrounds on an iPhone 14 Pro Max is a great way to create stunning photos that really stand out. In this blog post, we’ll explain what blurring backgrounds on an iPhone 14 Pro Max is, the benefits of doing so, and the steps you need to take to blur your backgrounds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Astonishing Trick: Easily Blur Backgrounds on Your iPhone 8 Without Portrait Mode!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/astonishing-trick-easily-blur-backgrounds-on-your-iphone-8-without-portrait-mode-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/astonishing-trick-easily-blur-backgrounds-on-your-iphone-8-without-portrait-mode-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you an iPhone 8 user looking for a way to blur backgrounds on your pictures without using Portrait Mode? If so, then this blog post is for you! In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ll explain what blurring backgrounds is, the benefits of blurring backgrounds, and how to blur backgrounds on your iPhone 8.
What is Blurring Backgrounds? Blurring backgrounds is a photography technique used to make the subject stand out by making the background less distinct.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlock the Secret to Professional-Looking iPhone Videos with This Simple Trick for Blur Backgrounds!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secret-to-professional-looking-iphone-videos-with-this-simple-trick-for-blur-backgrounds-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secret-to-professional-looking-iphone-videos-with-this-simple-trick-for-blur-backgrounds-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for a way to make your iPhone videos look more professional? Blurring the background of your videos is a simple trick that can make a huge difference in the overall look and feel of your video. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss what blur backgrounds are, the benefits of using them in your videos, and a step-by-step guide to blurring backgrounds on your iPhone videos.
Definition of Blur Backgrounds Blur backgrounds are when the background of a video is blurred so that the focus is on the subject in the foreground.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlock the Secret to Professional-Looking Photos with iPhone 13 Pro Max&#39;s Blurred Background Feature!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secret-to-professional-looking-photos-with-iphone-13-pro-max-s-blurred-background-feature-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secret-to-professional-looking-photos-with-iphone-13-pro-max-s-blurred-background-feature-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for a way to take your iPhone photos to the next level? Look no further than the new iPhone 13 Pro Max&amp;rsquo;s blurred background feature! This powerful feature can help you take professional-looking photos with ease. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll cover what the blurred background feature is, the benefits of using it, and how to use it to get the best results.
What is the Blurred Background Feature?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This iPhone Trick Will Instantly Give You Professional-Looking Videos With Blurred Backgrounds!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/this-iphone-trick-will-instantly-give-you-professional-looking-videos-with-blurred-backgrounds-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/this-iphone-trick-will-instantly-give-you-professional-looking-videos-with-blurred-backgrounds-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Do you want to create professional-looking videos with blurred backgrounds? If so, you’re in luck! This iPhone trick will instantly give you the ability to create stunning videos with blurred backgrounds.
Overview of iPhone&amp;rsquo;s Video Editing Capabilities The iPhone has a variety of video editing capabilities, including the ability to adjust the focus and blur the background of a video. It also has a range of filters and effects that can be used to enhance the look of a video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe the Results of this iPhone 8 Plus vs iPhone SE 2020 Camera Test!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-the-results-of-this-iphone-8-plus-vs-iphone-se-2020-camera-test-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-the-results-of-this-iphone-8-plus-vs-iphone-se-2020-camera-test-/</guid>
      <description>You Won&amp;rsquo;t Believe the Results of this iPhone 8 Plus vs iPhone SE 2020 Camera Test! Introduction The iPhone 8 Plus and the iPhone SE 2020 are two of the most popular iPhones on the market today. Both phones come with impressive camera specs, but which one takes the best pictures and videos? We recently conducted a camera test to find out the answer. Read on to find out the results of the iPhone 8 Plus vs iPhone SE 2020 camera test!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy It Is to Blur Backgrounds on iPhone 13 Photos!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-blur-backgrounds-on-iphone-13-photos-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-blur-backgrounds-on-iphone-13-photos-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Do you ever take photos on your iPhone 13 and wish you could make the background look a little more professional? Well, you&amp;rsquo;re in luck! With the latest update to the Photos app, you can now easily blur the background of your iPhone 13 photos with just a few taps.
Definition of Blurring Backgrounds on iPhone 13 Photos Blurring the background of a photo is a popular effect that can be used to draw attention to the subject of the photo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Astonishing Trick: Easily Blur Backgrounds on iPhone - Even When Not in Portrait Mode!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/astonishing-trick-easily-blur-backgrounds-on-iphone-even-when-not-in-portrait-mode-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/astonishing-trick-easily-blur-backgrounds-on-iphone-even-when-not-in-portrait-mode-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Do you want to blur the background of your iPhone photos? It&amp;rsquo;s easier than you think! You don&amp;rsquo;t even need to be in portrait mode to do it. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explain the trick to easily blur backgrounds on your iPhone, even when you&amp;rsquo;re not in portrait mode.
Definition of Blurring Backgrounds Blurring backgrounds is a photography technique that makes the subject of the photo stand out. It&amp;rsquo;s done by making the background out of focus and less detailed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
