<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>iTunes on Matiuswedos</title>
    <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/itunes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in iTunes on Matiuswedos</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/itunes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Unlock the Secret to Moving Music to Your iPhone Without iTunes - and It&#39;s Absolutely Free!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secret-to-moving-music-to-your-iphone-without-itunes-and-it-s-absolutely-free-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secret-to-moving-music-to-your-iphone-without-itunes-and-it-s-absolutely-free-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for a way to move music from your computer to your iPhone without using iTunes? If so, you’re in luck! There’s a free and easy way to do this, and you don’t need to be tech-savvy to make it happen.
In this blog post, we’ll discuss what it means to move music to your iPhone without iTunes, the benefits of doing so, and the steps you need to take to make it happen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discover the Secret to Easily Changing Your iPhone Backup Location in iTunes Windows 10!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/discover-the-secret-to-easily-changing-your-iphone-backup-location-in-itunes-windows-10-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/discover-the-secret-to-easily-changing-your-iphone-backup-location-in-itunes-windows-10-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you an iPhone user who has been struggling to figure out how to change your iPhone backup location in iTunes Windows 10? If so, you’ve come to the right place! In this blog post, we’ll discuss the definition of changing your iPhone backup location, the benefits of doing so, and the steps you need to take in order to change your iPhone backup location.
Definition of Changing iPhone Backup Location Changing your iPhone backup location is the process of moving the location of your iPhone backup files from the default location to a new location of your choosing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
