<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Performance on Matiuswedos</title>
    <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/performance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Performance on Matiuswedos</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/performance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Unglaubliche Vergleichstest: iPhone 13 Mini vs iPhone 8 - Welches ist besser?</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unglaubliche-vergleichstest-iphone-13-mini-vs-iphone-8-welches-ist-besser-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unglaubliche-vergleichstest-iphone-13-mini-vs-iphone-8-welches-ist-besser-/</guid>
      <description>Einleitung Es ist kein Geheimnis, dass Apple einer der führenden Anbieter von Smartphones ist. Die neueste Generation des iPhones, das iPhone 13 Mini, ist ein sehr beliebtes Gerät. Aber was ist mit dem älteren iPhone 8? Wie vergleichen sich die beiden Geräte? In diesem Blogpost werden wir uns die technischen Spezifikationen der beiden Geräte ansehen und herausfinden, welches besser ist.
Vergleich der technischen Spezifikationen iPhone 13 Mini Das iPhone 13 Mini hat ein 5,4-Zoll-OLED-Display mit einer Auflösung von 2436 x 1125 Pixeln.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What This iPhone SE 2020 Can Do - Test Results from Notebookcheck!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-this-iphone-se-2020-can-do-test-results-from-notebookcheck-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-this-iphone-se-2020-can-do-test-results-from-notebookcheck-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The iPhone SE 2020 is the latest addition to Apple&amp;rsquo;s lineup of iPhones. It&amp;rsquo;s a budget-friendly option that offers a great deal of features and performance for the price. But how well does it really perform? We put the iPhone SE 2020 to the test to find out.
Overview of the iPhone SE 2020 The iPhone SE 2020 is a 4.7-inch device that runs on Apple&amp;rsquo;s A13 Bionic processor. It has a 12MP rear camera, 7MP front-facing camera, and a Touch ID home button.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unbelievable Results: See which Android Tablet Comes Out on Top in Our Test of Price vs. Performance!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unbelievable-results-see-which-android-tablet-comes-out-on-top-in-our-test-of-price-vs-performance-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unbelievable-results-see-which-android-tablet-comes-out-on-top-in-our-test-of-price-vs-performance-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Android tablets are becoming increasingly popular, offering a range of features and capabilities at a variety of price points. But how do you know which tablet is the best for your needs? To help you decide, we put together a comprehensive test to compare the price versus performance of the most popular Android tablets on the market. Read on to find out which tablet comes out on top!
Definition of Android Tablet An Android tablet is a mobile computing device that runs on the Android operating system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unexpected Results of Our 300€ Android Tablet Test - You Won&#39;t Believe What We Found!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unexpected-results-of-our-300-android-tablet-test-you-won-t-believe-what-we-found-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unexpected-results-of-our-300-android-tablet-test-you-won-t-believe-what-we-found-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction We recently conducted a 300€ Android Tablet Test to evaluate the performance, battery life, and usability of a variety of devices. In this post, we&amp;rsquo;ll share our findings and discuss the unexpected results that we encountered.
Overview of the 300€ Android Tablet Test Our 300€ Android Tablet Test was conducted over the course of two weeks. We tested a total of 10 devices from different manufacturers and price ranges. We used a variety of benchmarking tools to evaluate the performance of each device, and we also tested the battery life and usability of each device.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
