<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>iPhone Settings on Matiuswedos</title>
    <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/iphone-settings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in iPhone Settings on Matiuswedos</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/iphone-settings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s the Quick and Easy Way to Turn Off SOS on Your iPhone 13!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/here-s-the-quick-and-easy-way-to-turn-off-sos-on-your-iphone-13-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/here-s-the-quick-and-easy-way-to-turn-off-sos-on-your-iphone-13-/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s the Quick and Easy Way to Turn Off SOS on Your iPhone 13 If you have an iPhone 13, you may have noticed the SOS feature that activates when you press and hold the side button. Although this feature can be useful in emergency situations, it can be a nuisance if it&amp;rsquo;s activated accidentally. Fortunately, it&amp;rsquo;s easy to turn off the SOS feature on your iPhone 13.
Introduction The SOS feature on the iPhone 13 is a safety feature that allows you to call emergency services with a single press and hold of the side button.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easily Turn Off Video Calls on Your iPhone - You Won&#39;t Believe How Simple It Is!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/easily-turn-off-video-calls-on-your-iphone-you-won-t-believe-how-simple-it-is-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/easily-turn-off-video-calls-on-your-iphone-you-won-t-believe-how-simple-it-is-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Video calls are a great way to connect with family, friends, and colleagues. iPhones have been able to make and receive video calls since the launch of FaceTime in 2010. However, some users may not want to have video calls enabled on their phones and may want to turn them off. In this blog post, we will explain how to easily turn off video calls on your iPhone.
Benefits of Turning Off Video Calls There are many benefits to turning off video calls on your iPhone.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
