<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Operating Systems on Matiuswedos</title>
    <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/operating-systems/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Operating Systems on Matiuswedos</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/operating-systems/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Revolutionize Your Setup: Use an Android Tablet as a Monitor on Linux via USB!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/revolutionize-your-setup-use-an-android-tablet-as-a-monitor-on-linux-via-usb-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/revolutionize-your-setup-use-an-android-tablet-as-a-monitor-on-linux-via-usb-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for a way to revolutionize your Linux setup? If so, then you should consider using an Android tablet as a monitor on Linux via USB! In this blog post, we will discuss the definition of an Android tablet, the benefits of using one as a monitor on Linux, and an overview of what is needed to set it up. We will also go over the steps required to set up the Android tablet, including connecting the tablet to the computer, installing necessary software, and configuring the system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlock the Secret SOS Feature in iOS 16 - Here&#39;s How to Find it on Your iPhone!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secret-sos-feature-in-ios-16-here-s-how-to-find-it-on-your-iphone-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secret-sos-feature-in-ios-16-here-s-how-to-find-it-on-your-iphone-/</guid>
      <description>IV. Conclusion
Introduction to the Secret SOS Feature in iOS 16 The new iOS 16 update includes a secret SOS feature that can be used to quickly contact emergency services. This feature is designed to provide users with an easy and secure way to access help in an emergency situation. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss what the SOS feature is, how to access it on your iPhone, and the benefits of using it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
