<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Networking on Matiuswedos</title>
    <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/networking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Networking on Matiuswedos</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/networking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>This Easy Trick Will Show You How to Scan QR Codes on Android to Instantly Connect to WiFi!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/this-easy-trick-will-show-you-how-to-scan-qr-codes-on-android-to-instantly-connect-to-wifi-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/this-easy-trick-will-show-you-how-to-scan-qr-codes-on-android-to-instantly-connect-to-wifi-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction QR codes are an easy and convenient way to connect to WiFi networks quickly and securely. With the right app, scanning QR codes on Android is a breeze. In this article, we’ll show you how to scan QR codes on Android and connect to WiFi networks in no time.
Definition of QR Code A QR code (or Quick Response code) is a type of barcode that contains information that can be read by a smartphone camera.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Surprise! You Can Easily Scan QR Codes on Samsung to Connect to WiFi - Here&#39;s How!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/surprise-you-can-easily-scan-qr-codes-on-samsung-to-connect-to-wifi-here-s-how-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/surprise-you-can-easily-scan-qr-codes-on-samsung-to-connect-to-wifi-here-s-how-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction QR codes have become a popular way to quickly and effortlessly connect to WiFi networks. With just a few simple steps, you can easily scan a QR code on your Samsung device and be connected to the internet in no time. In this blog post, we’ll explain what a QR code is, the benefits of using them, and how to scan a QR code on Samsung devices.
What is a QR Code?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlock the Secret to Locating Your iPhone&#39;s Mac Address Before Setup - You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy It Is!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secret-to-locating-your-iphone-s-mac-address-before-setup-you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secret-to-locating-your-iphone-s-mac-address-before-setup-you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction You may have heard of a Mac Address before, but do you know what it is and why it is important? A Mac Address is a unique identification number assigned to all network devices. It is used to identify and connect devices to a network. Knowing your Mac Address before you set up your iPhone can make the process easier and smoother. In this blog post, we will discuss how to locate your iPhone’s Mac Address before setting it up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlock the Secret to Finding Your Android Phone&#39;s IP Address - You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens Next!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secret-to-finding-your-android-phone-s-ip-address-you-won-t-believe-what-happens-next-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secret-to-finding-your-android-phone-s-ip-address-you-won-t-believe-what-happens-next-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever wanted to know your Android phone&amp;rsquo;s IP address? Well, you&amp;rsquo;re in luck! In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll be discussing the steps you need to take in order to find your Android phone&amp;rsquo;s IP address. We&amp;rsquo;ll also go over the benefits of knowing your Android phone&amp;rsquo;s IP address and the importance of it.
Definition of IP Address An IP address, or Internet Protocol address, is a unique identifier for a device connected to a computer network.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
