<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>How-to on Matiuswedos</title>
    <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/how-to/</link>
    <description>Recent content in How-to on Matiuswedos</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/how-to/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Astonishingly Easy: Learn How to Screen Record on iPhone 12 Pro Max with Sound in Just 5 Steps!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/astonishingly-easy-learn-how-to-screen-record-on-iphone-12-pro-max-with-sound-in-just-5-steps-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/astonishingly-easy-learn-how-to-screen-record-on-iphone-12-pro-max-with-sound-in-just-5-steps-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Screen Recording on iPhone 12 Pro Max Screen recording is a great way to capture what’s happening on your iPhone 12 Pro Max. It’s an easy way to capture your favorite moments and share them with friends and family. Plus, you can easily record audio with your recording, making it even more useful. In this article, we’ll show you how to easily screen record on your iPhone 12 Pro Max with sound in just 5 steps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Surprise! You Can Now Record Amazing Audio on Your Android Phone - Here&#39;s How!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/surprise-you-can-now-record-amazing-audio-on-your-android-phone-here-s-how-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/surprise-you-can-now-record-amazing-audio-on-your-android-phone-here-s-how-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Recording audio on your Android phone has never been easier! With the right app and a few simple steps, you can record amazing audio on your device. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll cover what recording audio on Android phones is, the benefits of recording audio on Android phones, and a step-by-step guide on how to record audio on your Android phone.
Definition of Recording Audio on Android Phones Recording audio on Android phones is the process of using your Android device to capture and record sound.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
