<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Apple iPhone on Matiuswedos</title>
    <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/apple-iphone/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Apple iPhone on Matiuswedos</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/apple-iphone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy it is to Turn Off Your iPhone 11 Pro Without a Screen!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-turn-off-your-iphone-11-pro-without-a-screen-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-turn-off-your-iphone-11-pro-without-a-screen-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you an iPhone 11 Pro user who is looking for an easier way to turn off your device? Then you won&amp;rsquo;t believe how easy it is to turn off your iPhone 11 Pro without a screen!
Overview of iPhone 11 Pro The iPhone 11 Pro is one of the most popular smartphones on the market. It has a sleek design, powerful processor, and a great camera. It also has a large 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Life-Changing Trick Will Teach You How to Hard Reset Your iPhone 13 Pro Max in 5 Minutes!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/this-life-changing-trick-will-teach-you-how-to-hard-reset-your-iphone-13-pro-max-in-5-minutes-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/this-life-changing-trick-will-teach-you-how-to-hard-reset-your-iphone-13-pro-max-in-5-minutes-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for a way to hard reset your iPhone 13 Pro Max? If so, you’re in luck! In this blog post, we’ll walk you through the step-by-step process of hard resetting your iPhone 13 Pro Max in just five minutes.
What is a Hard Reset? A hard reset is a process that erases all of the data and settings on your device and restores it to its original factory settings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revolutionary New iPhone 12 Pro with 128 GB - Get Yours Now with a Contract!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/revolutionary-new-iphone-12-pro-with-128-gb-get-yours-now-with-a-contract-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/revolutionary-new-iphone-12-pro-with-128-gb-get-yours-now-with-a-contract-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you ready to upgrade your current iPhone to the revolutionary new iPhone 12 Pro with 128 GB of storage? If so, you’re in luck! The iPhone 12 Pro is the latest and greatest offering from Apple, and it’s packed with features that will take your mobile experience to the next level. In this blog post, we’ll take a look at the features and benefits of the iPhone 12 Pro, and explain how you can get your own with a contract.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Surprise Trick: Easily Backup Your iPhone Directly to an External Hard Drive on Windows!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/surprise-trick-easily-backup-your-iphone-directly-to-an-external-hard-drive-on-windows-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/surprise-trick-easily-backup-your-iphone-directly-to-an-external-hard-drive-on-windows-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Do you need to backup your iPhone data to an external hard drive on Windows? It can be challenging to figure out how to do this. Fortunately, with the help of iTunes, you can easily backup your iPhone directly to an external hard drive on Windows. In this blog post, we will discuss the steps to backup your iPhone to an external hard drive on Windows.
Steps to Backup iPhone to External Hard Drive on Windows Connect iPhone and External Hard Drive The first step is to connect your iPhone and external hard drive to your Windows computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlock the Secret to Resetting Your iPhone 6s Without a Password!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secret-to-resetting-your-iphone-6s-without-a-password-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secret-to-resetting-your-iphone-6s-without-a-password-/</guid>
      <description>I. Introduction Having trouble resetting your iPhone 6s? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, we&amp;rsquo;ve got you covered! Resetting your iPhone 6s without a password is a surprisingly easy and straightforward task. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through the steps to do so.
II. Steps for Resetting Your iPhone 6s Without a Password Connect your iPhone 6s to your computer with a USB cable.
Open iTunes and select your iPhone 6s from the list of devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revolutionäres iPhone 12 Pro Max 256GB Jetzt Ohne Vertrag bei Telekom Erhältlich!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/revolution-res-iphone-12-pro-max-256gb-jetzt-ohne-vertrag-bei-telekom-erh-ltlich-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/revolution-res-iphone-12-pro-max-256gb-jetzt-ohne-vertrag-bei-telekom-erh-ltlich-/</guid>
      <description>Ein revolutionäres iPhone 12 Pro Max 256GB jetzt ohne Vertrag bei Telekom erhältlich! Das iPhone 12 Pro Max 256GB ist ab sofort bei der Telekom ohne Vertrag erhältlich. Es ist die neueste Generation des iPhones und bietet eine beeindruckende Leistung und eine Vielzahl von Funktionen. Es verfügt über ein Super-Retina XDR-Display, eine 5G-Verbindung und eine verbesserte Kamera. Es ist das leistungsstärkste iPhone, das je gebaut wurde.
Die Vorteile des revolutionären iPhone 12 Pro Max 256GB Das iPhone 12 Pro Max 256GB verfügt über ein 6,7-Zoll-Super-Retina XDR-Display, das eine brillante Farbwiedergabe und eine gestochen scharfe Auflösung bietet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This One Trick Will Help You Turn Off Your iPhone 11 Even If The Screen Is Broken!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/this-one-trick-will-help-you-turn-off-your-iphone-11-even-if-the-screen-is-broken-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/this-one-trick-will-help-you-turn-off-your-iphone-11-even-if-the-screen-is-broken-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you an iPhone 11 user who is having trouble turning off your device because the screen is broken? If so, this blog post is for you!
Overview of the Issue It can be incredibly frustrating when your iPhone 11 screen is broken and you can’t turn off the device. This can be especially problematic if you’re trying to repair the device or if you’re trying to protect your data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This 1 Simple Trick Will Let You Backup Your iPhone Directly to an External Hard Drive in Windows 10!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/this-1-simple-trick-will-let-you-backup-your-iphone-directly-to-an-external-hard-drive-in-windows-10-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/this-1-simple-trick-will-let-you-backup-your-iphone-directly-to-an-external-hard-drive-in-windows-10-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Backing up your iPhone is an essential part of protecting your data and ensuring that you don’t lose important files in the event of a crash or theft. While iCloud is a great option for backing up your iPhone, it’s not always the most convenient. Fortunately, there’s a simple trick that will allow you to back up your iPhone directly to an external hard drive in Windows 10.
Definition of an External Hard Drive An external hard drive is a type of storage device that connects to your computer via USB.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazing Trick: Easily Backup Your iPhone to an External Hard Drive in Windows 11!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/amazing-trick-easily-backup-your-iphone-to-an-external-hard-drive-in-windows-11-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/amazing-trick-easily-backup-your-iphone-to-an-external-hard-drive-in-windows-11-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction We all know how important it is to back up our data, especially when it comes to our iPhones. But, it can be tricky to know how to do it properly. In this blog post, we’ll show you an easy way to back up your iPhone to an external hard drive in Windows 11.
Definition of an External Hard Drive An external hard drive is a storage device that connects to your computer through a USB port.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Help You Hard Reset Your iPhone 13 When It&#39;s Frozen - You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens Next!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-help-you-hard-reset-your-iphone-13-when-it-s-frozen-you-won-t-believe-what-happens-next-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-help-you-hard-reset-your-iphone-13-when-it-s-frozen-you-won-t-believe-what-happens-next-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Do you have an iPhone 13 that&amp;rsquo;s been frozen or unresponsive? If so, you&amp;rsquo;re not alone. Many users have encountered this issue and don&amp;rsquo;t know what to do. Fortunately, there is a simple trick that can help you hard reset your iPhone 13 when it&amp;rsquo;s frozen. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss what a hard reset is, why it&amp;rsquo;s important to know how to do one, and provide a step-by-step guide to help you hard reset your iPhone 13.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlock the Secret: Discover How to Easily Put Screen Record on Your iPhone 11 Pro Max!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secret-discover-how-to-easily-put-screen-record-on-your-iphone-11-pro-max-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secret-discover-how-to-easily-put-screen-record-on-your-iphone-11-pro-max-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Screen Recording on iPhone 11 Pro Max Screen recording is a powerful tool for capturing a digital device’s display. It can be used to capture tutorials, presentations, or even gameplay. With the release of the iPhone 11 Pro Max, Apple has made it easier than ever to record your iPhone’s screen. In this article, we’ll discuss the basics of screen recording and provide a step-by-step guide for getting started.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
