<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Food &amp; Beverage on Matiuswedos</title>
    <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/food-beverage/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Food &amp; Beverage on Matiuswedos</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matiuswedos.github.io/tags/food-beverage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When You Check Your Tim Hortons Roll Up the Rim!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-check-your-tim-hortons-roll-up-the-rim-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-check-your-tim-hortons-roll-up-the-rim-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Tim Hortons Roll Up the Rim If you&amp;rsquo;re a fan of Tim Hortons, then you know that one of the best parts of their coffee is the chance to win some amazing prizes with their Roll Up the Rim contest. Every year, customers get the chance to roll up the rim of their coffee cup and see if they&amp;rsquo;ve won a prize. It&amp;rsquo;s a fun way to get a little something extra with your coffee and it&amp;rsquo;s a great way to show your loyalty to the brand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When You Play Tim Hortons Roll Up the Rim to Win!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-play-tim-hortons-roll-up-the-rim-to-win-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-play-tim-hortons-roll-up-the-rim-to-win-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for an exciting way to win fantastic prizes? Then you should definitely check out Tim Hortons Roll Up the Rim to Win! This popular promotion has been around for years and is a great way to get your hands on some awesome prizes.
Overview of Tim Hortons Roll Up the Rim to Win Tim Hortons Roll Up the Rim to Win is an annual promotion that takes place at participating Tim Hortons locations in Canada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When You Download the Tim Hortons Roll Up The Rim App!</title>
      <link>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-download-the-tim-hortons-roll-up-the-rim-app-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiuswedos.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-download-the-tim-hortons-roll-up-the-rim-app-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you a fan of Tim Hortons&amp;rsquo; Roll Up The Rim? If so, you won&amp;rsquo;t believe what happens when you download the Tim Hortons Roll Up The Rim App! This app is the perfect way to get the most out of your Tim Hortons experience.
What is the Tim Hortons Roll Up The Rim App? The Tim Hortons Roll Up The Rim App is an easy-to-use mobile application designed to enhance your experience with Tim Hortons.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
